[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
What's wrong with him?
ماذا حل به؟
Look. What's wrong with him?
ينظر.  ماذا حل به؟
It was a dream.
كان حلما.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
[Mr. Lin.]
[السيد.  لين.]
[There's trouble.]
[هناك مشكلة.]
[Zhang Hao Cheng was arrested by the police.]
[ألقت الشرطة القبض على تشانغ هاو تشنغ.]
[Episode 35]
[الحلقة 35]
[Eight Hours]
[ثماني ساعات]
He's here.
إنه هنا.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
Please answer our question.
الرجاء الإجابة على سؤالنا.
Please answer.
من فضلك أجب.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
What Zhang Hao Cheng has done
ما فعله تشانغ هاو تشنغ
has nothing to do with me
لا علاقة لي به
or our group.
أو مجموعتنا.
There's only one thing I care about now.
هناك شيء واحد فقط أهتم به الآن.
How much did you hide from me
كم اخفيت عني
about the 2021 code error?
حول خطأ رمز 2021؟
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
We just knew it too.
لقد عرفنا ذلك أيضًا.
Shut up!
اسكت!
You signed the contract with Magellan Group.
لقد وقعت العقد مع Magellan Group.
You said you didn't know, did you?
قلت أنك لا تعرف ، أليس كذلك؟
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
actively cooperate with the police
تتعاون بنشاط مع الشرطة
to strictly check all the people involved.
للتحقق بدقة من جميع الأشخاص المعنيين.
Allocate all resources
تخصيص جميع الموارد
of the group
من المجموعة
to solve the 2021 code error.
لحل خطأ كود 2021.
Save the trapped online users.
حفظ المستخدمين المحاصرين عبر الإنترنت.
I'll try my best
سأبذل جهدي
to save them
لإنقاذهم
at all costs.
باي ثمن.
And
و
I want to remind
اريد ان اذكر
those who disobey me
أولئك الذين يعصونني
and withhold information.
ويحجب المعلومات.
Wait and see.
انتظر و شاهد.
I'll find you out
سأجدك
one by one.
واحدا تلو الآخر.
I'll lead this special investigation team.
سأقود فريق التحقيق الخاص هذا.
Let Bai Wei be the deputy leader.
دع باي وي يكون نائب الزعيم.
But her qualification...
لكن مؤهلها ...
Dismiss.
رفض.
Move!
يتحرك!
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Ye Tian.
أيها تيان.
Wei Wei.
وي وي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I lied to you.
لقد كذبت عليك.
Invincible is holding a letter
الذي لا يقهر يحمل رسالة
I left for you.
لقد غادرت من أجلك.
Lied to me?
كذبت علي؟
What does it mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Why did
لماذا فعلت
the non-player character evolve?
تتطور شخصية غير اللاعب؟
Like a terminator.
مثل فاصل.
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
It's not a good thing, anyway.
إنه ليس شيئًا جيدًا ، على أي حال.
Xiao Liang, look over there.
شياو ليانغ ، انظر هناك.
Everybody.
الجميع.
General Long Wei of Autumn City
عام لونغ وي لمدينة الخريف
is right behind me.
ورائي مباشرة.
Why doesn't he stay in the main city
لماذا لا يقيم في المدينة الرئيسية
but come here instead?
لكن تعال إلى هنا بدلاً من ذلك؟
Let me guess.
دعني أخمن.
He may be
انه قد يكون
Pangu's new boss
رئيس بانغو الجديد
next season.
الموسم القادم.
Awesome.
رائع.
Why is Pangu getting more and more strange?
لماذا تزداد غرابة بانغو؟
Da Tou.
دا تو.
Let's go back to Autumn City.
دعنا نعود إلى مدينة الخريف.
We have to tell Ms. Wei now.
علينا إخبار السيدة وي الآن.
Okay.
تمام.
Invincible.
لا يقهر.
Where is he?
أين هو؟
He...
هو...
He left this letter for you.
لقد ترك هذه الرسالة لك.
Then he left.
ثم غادر.
When did he leave?
متى غادر؟
He left long ago.
لقد غادر منذ فترة طويلة.
Ms. Wei.
السيدة وي.
He was not in a good state
لم يكن في حالة جيدة
when he left.
عندما غادر.
He looked like
وقال انه يتطلع مثل
he would die on the battlefield in a drama.
سيموت في ساحة المعركة في دراما.
Don't talk nonsense.
لا تتحدث عن هراء.
I'm leaving.
سأرحل.
Don't come to me.
لا تأتي إلي.
And you have to go offline as soon as possible.
وعليك أن تكون غير متصل بالإنترنت في أسرع وقت ممكن.
Don't log in to Pangu anymore.
لا تقم بتسجيل الدخول إلى Pangu بعد الآن.
The number of 2021 code errors
عدد أخطاء كود 2021
is far more than we thought.
أكثر بكثير مما كنا نظن.
I can't stop it anymore.
لا أستطيع التوقف عن ذلك بعد الآن.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I let you down.
خذلتك.
Forget me,
انساني،
Wei Wei.
وي وي.
Please.
رجاء.
Ye Tian, you fool.
أيها تيان ، أيها الأحمق.
Which direction did he go?
في أي اتجاه ذهب؟
I have no idea.
ليس لدي فكره.
Why didn't you stop him?
لماذا لم توقفه؟
Stop him?
أوقفوه؟
Do you think
هل تعتقد
I can stop him?
يمكنني منعه؟
Everybody,
الجميع،
he's not like
هو ليس مثل
a non-player character.
شخصية غير لاعب.
Look at his moves.
انظر إلى تحركاته.
How smooth.
كيف السلس.
Amazing.
مدهش.
He seems to have seen me.
يبدو أنه رآني.
Everybody.
الجميع.
I'm risking my life live streaming.
أنا أخاطر بحياتي في البث المباشر.
He's gone.
لقد رحل.
I'll continue to follow him.
سأستمر في متابعته.
Ms. Wei.
السيدة وي.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
All the mosaics have gone
اختفت كل الفسيفساء
into General Long Wei's body.
في جسد الجنرال لونغ وي.
A... All?
أ ... كل شيء؟
Yes.
نعم.
Ms. Wei.
السيدة وي.
Ye Tian doesn't want to talk to you.
يي تيان لا تريد التحدث معك.
It's no use sending him a message.
لا فائدة من إرسال رسالة إليه.
I can find him
يمكنني أن أجده
if I insist.
إذا أصررت.
[Please leave a message after the tone.]
[الرجاء ترك رسالة بعد النغمة.]
Bai Wei.
باي وي.
I really need your skills now.
أنا حقا بحاجة إلى مهاراتك الآن.
If you hear the message,
إذا سمعت الرسالة ،
call me as soon as possible.
اتصل بي في أقرب وقت ممكن.
Check Bai Wei's online record.
تحقق من سجل باي وي على الإنترنت.
Last night?
اخر مساء؟
Check Bai Wei's operation record
تحقق من سجل عمليات باي وي
in the original server.
في الخادم الأصلي.
Restore the initial state
استعادة الحالة الأولية
of GM 001.
من GM 001.
Bai Wei and Ye Tian.
باي وي ويي تيان.
Why on earth?
لماذا بحق الارض؟
User GM 001.
المستخدم GM 001.
Status online.
الحالة متصل.
Location unknown.
الموقع غير معروف.
Xiao Tian.
شياو تيان.
You're still alive.
انت لازلت حيا.
You didn't kill me.
أنت لم تقتلني.
Impossible!
مستحيل!
Actually, I've always been by your side.
في الواقع ، كنت دائمًا بجانبك.
No way.
مستحيل.
That was just a dream.
إنه كان مجرد حلم.
There must be something wrong with the system.
يجب أن يكون هناك خطأ ما في النظام.
Check Sea of Flowers' account for me.
تحقق من حساب Sea of ​​Flowers لي.
Sea of Flowers, heroine.
بحر الزهور ، البطلة.
Location unknown.
الموقع غير معروف.
Show me all the tasks
أرني كل المهام
that GM 001
أن GM 001
and Sea of Flowers
وبحر الزهور
have done in Pangu.
فعلت في بانغو.
Sea of Flowers
بحر الزهور
and GM 001
و GM 001
completed the Mount Qingtian task together.
أكملوا مهمة جبل تشينغتيان معًا.
Come on. Hold it.
تعال.  أمسك به.
-You're feeble. Do you lack calcium?
-أنت ضعيف.  هل تفتقر إلى الكالسيوم؟  -أنت ضعيف.  هل تفتقر إلى الكالسيوم؟
Sea of Flowers
بحر الزهور
and GM 001
و GM 001
completed the Sword Cottage special task together.
أكملوا مهمة Sword Cottage الخاصة معًا.
Sea of Flowers
بحر الزهور
and GM 001
و GM 001
completed the Black Forest task together.
أكملوا مهمة الغابة السوداء معًا.
Wei Wei.
وي وي.
This beast is like a dog. It has a weak waist.
هذا الوحش مثل الكلب.  لديها خصر ضعيف.
Its weak point is in its waist.
ضعفه في وسطه.
Let's attack its vital part.
دعونا نهاجم الجزء الحيوي.
So you've been together
إذا كنتم معا
since the beginning.
منذ البداية.
Bai Wei didn't think
لم يفكر باي وي
Xiao Tian was unconscious from the beginning.
كان شياو تيان فاقدًا للوعي منذ البداية.
I'm too dumb.
أنا غبية جدا.
Sea of Flowers
بحر الزهور
and GM 001
و GM 001
completed the only bonus task
أكمل مهمة المكافأة الوحيدة
of Love Flower Village.
قرية زهرة الحب.
They got married
لقد تزوجوا
and learned Dual Cultivation.
وتعلمت الزراعة المزدوجة.
Dual Cultivation?
زراعة مزدوجة؟
Old man.
رجل عجوز.
I'll make up
سوف أعوض
for your crimes one by one.
لجرائمك واحدًا تلو الآخر.
Ms. Zhang.
السيدة تشانغ.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
I...
أنا...
I want to see my cousin.
اريد ان ارى ابن عمي.
Go in.
أدخل.
Yi Da.
نعم.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Xiao Tian.
شياو تيان.
It's been a while.
لقد مر وقت طويل.
Mdm. Chen.
ام دي ام.  تشين.
It's just a remnant image.
إنها مجرد صورة متبقية.
Why are you also recycled by the recycle bin?
لماذا يتم إعادة تدويرها أيضًا بواسطة سلة المحذوفات؟
No.
لا.
You're the first patient of 2021.
أنت أول مريض في عام 2021.
When designing Pangu,
عند تصميم Pangu ،
I used to upload your cognitive data chain information.
اعتدت على تحميل معلومات سلسلة البيانات المعرفية الخاصة بك.
It's the root cause of the 2021 code error.
إنه السبب الجذري لخطأ رمز 2021.
It's all my fault.
هذا كله خطأي.
Xiao Tian.
شياو تيان.
It's been a while.
لقد مر وقت طويل.
Mdm. Chen.
ام دي ام.  تشين.
Do you know that?
هل تعرف أن؟
I founded Pangu with all I have
لقد قمت بتأسيس Pangu بكل ما لدي
because I want to create
لأنني أريد أن أخلق
a new and different world
عالم جديد ومختلف
for everyone.
للجميع.
But in the end, I found that
لكن في النهاية ، وجدت ذلك
I couldn't change anything.
لم أستطع تغيير أي شيء.
There's no perfect thing in the world.
لا يوجد شيء مثالي في العالم.
Nothing
لا شيئ
is perfect.
مثالي.
I should have realized this earlier.
كان يجب أن أدرك هذا في وقت سابق.
It's just like I can't save everyone.
يبدو الأمر وكأنني لا أستطيع إنقاذ الجميع.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I promised you
انا وعدتك
I'd take good care of Wei Wei.
سأعتني جيدًا بـ Wei Wei.
But I can't do it.
لكن لا يمكنني فعل ذلك.
I can't just stand by
لا يمكنني الوقوف جانبا فقط
and let her take risks for me.
ودعها تخاطر من أجلي.
I thought I wasn't afraid of death.
اعتقدت أنني لم أكن خائفًا من الموت.
But
لكن
after entering Pangu,
بعد دخول Pangu ،
I realized
أدركت
I wasn't as strong as I thought.
لم أكن قوية كما اعتقدت.
I love her.
أنا أحبها.
I can't bear to leave her.
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل تركها.
Mom.
أم.
Wei Wei.
وي وي.
This is the remnant image of Mdm. Chen.
هذه هي الصورة المتبقية من Mdm.  تشين.
It's virtual.
إنها افتراضية.
Ye Tian.
أيها تيان.
Do you remember
هل تذكر
when my mother was alive,
عندما كانت والدتي على قيد الحياة ،
you promised her
لقد وعدتها
to build Pangu
لبناء Pangu
into a world of infinite possibilities
في عالم من الاحتمالات اللانهائية
to continue her unfulfilled dreams?
لمواصلة أحلامها التي لم تتحقق؟
Infinite possibilities?
إمكانيات غير محدودة؟
Nothing is impossible.
لا شيء مستحيل.
Xiao Liang said I can't find you.
قال شياو ليانغ لا أستطيع أن أجدك.
I found you, didn't I?
لقد وجدتك ، أليس كذلك؟
So as long as
طالما أن
we don't give up,
نحن لا نستسلم
we can find a way to save Pangu.
يمكننا إيجاد طريقة لإنقاذ بانغو.
Weren't you a believer in miracles?
ألم تكن مؤمناً بالمعجزات؟
Neither Uncle Ye nor my mother
لا عم يي ولا أمي
wanted to see you
أراد رؤيتك
give up so easily.
تستسلم بسهولة.
And
و
didn't you promise to
لم تعد ل
stay with me for the rest of your life?
ابق معي لبقية حياتك؟
Why did you leave me behind?
لماذا تركتني ورائي؟
You still owe me an apology.
أنت لا تزال تدين لي بالاعتذار.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
It's okay.
حسنا.
August 2nd, 8:00 a.m.
2 أغسطس ، 8:00 صباحًا
Bai Wei was online.
كان باي وي على الإنترنت.
Ye Tian was offline.
كان يي تيان غير متصل بالإنترنت.
August 2nd, 8:00 p.m.
2 أغسطس ، 8:00 مساءً
Bai Wei was offline.
كان باي وي غير متصل بالإنترنت.
Ye Tian was online.
كان يي تيان متصلاً بالإنترنت.
So you've been with me all the time.
لذلك كنت معي طوال الوقت.
Actually, I've always been by your side.
في الواقع ، كنت دائمًا بجانبك.
No way. Impossible.
مستحيل.  مستحيل.
Lin Feng.
لين فنغ.
Quit it.
اقلع عنها اتركها.
Simba.
سيمبا.
I can't accept
لا يمكنني القبول
what you gave me.
ماذا اعطيتني.
It's not an ordinary stone
إنه ليس حجرًا عاديًا
but Star Moonstone.
لكن ستار مونستون.
Why haven't I thought of
لماذا لم أفكر في
such a simple thing.
مثل هذا الشيء البسيط.
From today onwards,
من اليوم فصاعدا،
you're the controller with
أنت المتحكم مع
the highest authority of Celeste Group.
أعلى سلطة في مجموعة سيليست.
You're my best brother.
أنت أخي المفضل.
You're unique in my heart.
أنت فريد في قلبي.
Whether it's before, now or in the future,
سواء كان ذلك من قبل أو الآن أو في المستقبل ،
you're the one who loves Celeste Group most.
أنت أكثر من يحب سيليست جروب.
I don't want you going to the bad.
لا أريدك أن تذهب إلى السوء.
Welcome.
أهلا بك.
What would you like, Miss?
ماذا تريدين يا آنسة؟
It's okay, thank you.
لا بأس ، شكرا لك.
All right.
حسنا.
You're so sure I'll come.
أنت متأكد من أنني سأحضر.
I wasn't sure.
لم أكن متأكدا.
After all, I made
بعد كل شيء ، لقد صنعت
so many unforgivable mistakes.
الكثير من الأخطاء التي لا تغتفر.
I'm glad you know it.
أنا سعيد لأنك تعلم ذلك.
But
لكن
no matter what wrong I did,
بغض النظر عن الخطأ الذي فعلته ،
you and Xiao Tian
أنت وشياو تيان
are always willing to give me a chance.
دائما على استعداد لمنحي فرصة.
Right?
حق؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
He came to see me yesterday.
جاء لرؤيتي أمس.
He said he'd give me another chance.
قال إنه سيعطيني فرصة أخرى.
And
و
I also want to be
انا ايضا اريد ان اكون
who I used to be.
على ما اعتدت أن أكون.
Did Xiao Tian
هل شياو تيان
come to see you?
تأتي لرؤيتك؟
Didn't he...
ألم يكن ...
He woke up once yesterday.
استيقظ مرة أمس.
He also asked me
كما سألني
to help him save Pangu
لمساعدته في إنقاذ بانغو
and those trapped users.
وهؤلاء المستخدمين المحاصرين.
He even gave me this.
حتى أنه أعطاني هذا.
He said he'd forgive me
قال إنه سيسامحني
after everything was done.
بعد أن تم كل شيء.
No way.
مستحيل.
Linda.
ليندا.
I hope you can come back
آمل أن تتمكن من العودة
and work with me
واعمل معي
to overcome the 2021 code error.
للتغلب على خطأ رمز 2021.
And then?
وثم؟
Then I promised Xiao Tian that
ثم وعدت شياو تيان بذلك
I'd turn myself in
كنت سأسلم نفسي
and bear all the punishment I deserve.
وأتحمل كل العقوبة التي أستحقها.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll come back.
سوف ارجع.
But
لكن
it's not for Xiao Tian
إنه ليس شياو تيان
but you.
لكنك.
The one I once loved.
الذي أحببته ذات مرة.
Right.
الصحيح.
Once loved.
أحب مرة واحدة.
Yes.
نعم.
I hope
آمل
you can find your original self.
يمكنك أن تجد نفسك الأصلي.
I believe we'll forgive you
أعتقد أننا سوف نغفر لك
if you're willing
إذا كنت ترغب في ذلك
to make up for it.
للتعويض عن ذلك.
I'll try my best
سأبذل جهدي
to make up for all my mistakes.
لتعويض كل أخطائي.
Before that,
قبل ذلك،
I think you need to meet someone.
أعتقد أنك بحاجة لمقابلة شخص ما.
The one who has been deeply hurt by you.
الشخص الذي جرحته بشدة.
You're finally here.
أنت هنا أخيرًا.
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
Your dad...
والدك ...
You didn't
لم تفعل
come to me for him, right?
تعال لي من أجله ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
I didn't.
لم أكن.
I saw the news.
رأيت الأخبار.
You announced you'd save Pangu
لقد أعلنت أنك ستوفر Pangu
and become a hero.
ويصبح بطلا.
You need to devote yourself to it.
تحتاج إلى تكريس نفسك لذلك.
And
و
I'm a stone in your heart.
أنا حجر في قلبك.
That's why you need
لهذا السبب تحتاج
my forgiveness to feel at ease, right?
مسامحتي للشعور بالراحة ، أليس كذلك؟
I'm really sorry about
أنا حقا آسف
what happened between us.
ما حدث بيننا.
I'll make up for it.
سوف أعوض عن ذلك.
I don't need it.
لا أحتاجه.
I don't need your apology either.
أنا لست بحاجة إلى اعتذارك أيضًا.
Because I was wrong, too.
لأنني كنت مخطئا أيضا.
Do you know
هل تعرف
I once asked someone to kidnap you?
ذات مرة طلبت من شخص ما أن يخطفك؟
I wonder if
أتساءل عما إذا كان
you can stay with me
يمكنك البقاء معي
all the time like this.
طوال الوقت مثل هذا.
Do you find me ridiculous?
هل تجدني سخيف؟
If I
اذا انا
hadn't done so,
لم تفعل ذلك ،
my dad wouldn't
والدي لا
have been arrested.
تم القبض عليه.
I wouldn't have known
لم أكن لأعرف
how cruel he is to others
كم هو قاسٍ على الآخرين
and how good he is to me.
وكم هو جيد بالنسبة لي.
Lin Feng.
لين فنغ.
Only now do I know
الآن فقط أعرف
how annoying
كم هذا مستفز
and capricious
ومتقلبة
I was.
انا كنت.
So
وبالتالي
I won't blame you for
لن ألومك على ذلك
what you've done to me.
ماذا فعلت لي.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Don't look at me like that.
لا تنظر إلي هكذا.
It's true.
انها حقيقة.
I just figured out a lot of things.
لقد اكتشفت للتو الكثير من الأشياء.
Actually,
في الواقع،
I don't love you as much as I thought.
أنا لا أحبك بقدر ما اعتقدت.
All I love
كل ما أحبه
is myself, who loves you crazily.
هو نفسي الذي يحبك بجنون.
Do you understand?
هل تفهم؟
It doesn't matter whether
لا يهم ما إذا كان
you understand or not.
فهمت أم لا.
Lin Feng.
لين فنغ.
Now we're square.
نحن الآن مربعون.
Try your best to do what you want.
ابذل قصارى جهدك لتفعل ما تريد.
Because I have something I want to do.
لأن لدي شيء أريد أن أفعله.
Good luck.
حظًا سعيدًا.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
There's
هناك
such a big hidden danger in Pangu.
مثل هذا الخطر الخفي الكبير في بانغو.
Did the police get involved?
هل تدخلت الشرطة؟
We'll fully
سنقوم بشكل كامل
cooperate with the police.
التعاون مع الشرطة.
We'll fix this code error at all costs
سنقوم بإصلاح خطأ الرمز هذا بأي ثمن
as soon as possible.
في أقرب وقت ممكن.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
There are 134 infected users
هناك 134 مستخدم مصاب
who can't go offline now.
الذين لا يستطيعون الذهاب إلى وضع عدم الاتصال الآن.
Is it the official accurate figure
هل هو الرقم الرسمي الدقيق
or more than that?
أو أكثر من ذلك؟
The number is accurate.
الرقم دقيق.
The 134 users
الـ 134 مستخدما
who can't go offline,
الذين لا يستطيعون الذهاب إلى وضع عدم الاتصال ،
whether online or offline,
سواء عبر الإنترنت أو غير متصل ،
should be fully protected by our group.
يجب أن تكون محمية بالكامل من قبل مجموعتنا.
I can promise that
يمكنني أن أعدك بذلك
these users who can't go offline
هؤلاء المستخدمين الذين لا يمكنهم الانتقال إلى وضع عدم الاتصال
will be safe.
سيكون آمنا.
Here I'd like to urge
هنا أود أن أحث
users who are still online
المستخدمين الذين ما زالوا متصلين بالإنترنت
in Pangu to go offline immediately.
في بانغو للذهاب إلى وضع عدم الاتصال على الفور.
Don't do anything related to Pangu
لا تفعل أي شيء متعلق بـ Pangu
until we find a solution.
حتى نجد حلا.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
There's such a big hidden danger in Pangu.
يوجد مثل هذا الخطر الخفي الكبير في بانغو.
Which department head of Celeste Group
أي قسم رئيس مجموعة سيليست
should bear the greatest responsibility?
يجب أن تتحمل أكبر قدر من المسؤولية؟
I'll take full responsibility.
سأتحمل المسؤولية الكاملة.
Matron.
ماترون.
Can you help me check
هل يمكنك مساعدتي في التحقق
my child's condition now?
حالة طفلي الآن؟
It's been so long now.
لقد مر وقت طويل الآن.
Everything is normal.
كل شيئ طبيعي.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
With Ms. Zhang, everything's good.
مع السيدة تشانغ ، كل شيء على ما يرام.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Okay then.
حسنا إذا.
Trust us.
ثق بنا.
All right.
حسنا.
We're all here.
كلنا هنا.
Okay.
تمام.
What's the matter, Ms. Zhang?
ما الأمر يا سيدة تشانغ؟
Hello, I'd like to know
مرحبًا ، أود أن أعرف
how the condition is now.
كيف الحال الآن.
All patients' physical indicators are normal.
جميع المؤشرات الجسدية للمرضى طبيعية.
That's good.
هذا طيب.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
The person in charge?
الشخص المسؤول؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'm the person in charge here
أنا الشخص المسؤول هنا
before the group can find a solution.
قبل أن تتمكن المجموعة من إيجاد حل.
I saw the news.
رأيت الأخبار.
She is Zhang Hao Cheng's daughter.
هي ابنة Zhang Hao Cheng.
It was all Zhang Hao Cheng's fault.
كان كل خطأ Zhang Hao Cheng.
Zhang Hao Cheng's daughter?
ابنة تشانغ هاو تشنغ؟
Come on.
تعال.
Go and have a look.
اذهب والقى نظرة.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
What's the use of money?
ما فائدة المال؟
I want my son!
اريد ابني!
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Don't be hypocritical.
لا تكن نفاق.
Look!
ينظر!
Calm down!
اهدأ!
You can't solve the problem this way.
لا يمكنك حل المشكلة بهذه الطريقة.
I don't want to see you!
لا اريد ان اراك!
You hypocrite!
أنت منافق!
Get out of here! Give us back our kids!
اخرج من هنا!  أعيدوا لنا أطفالنا!
Solve the problem!
حل المشكلة!
You...
أنت...
Well done!
أحسنت!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Go away. We don't want to see you.
يبتعد.  لا نريد رؤيتك.
Good! You deserve a slap!
حسن!  أنت تستحق صفعة!
How immoral you are.
كم أنت غير أخلاقي.
Give my son back!
أعيدوا ابني!
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I know it's all my dad's fault.
أعلم أن هذا كله خطأ والدي.
I know you won't forgive him either.
أعلم أنك لن تسامحه أيضًا.
I'm just like you.
انا مثلك تماما.
I also hate him very much.
أنا أيضا أكرهه كثيرا.
But he's my dad.
لكنه والدي.
He didn't leave me
لم يتركني
when I needed him most.
عندما كنت في أمس الحاجة إليه.
I can't leave him now.
لا أستطيع تركه الآن.
I'll take all the blame.
سآخذ كل اللوم.
Please believe me.
أرجوك صدقني.
Please.
رجاء.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I'm really sorry.
أنا حقا آسف.
I'm sorry, everyone.
أنا آسف للجميع.
Sorry.
آسف.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Sorry, everyone.
اعتذر للجميع.
What's the use? Honestly.
ما الفائدة؟  بصدق.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Dad.
أب.
There's something that
هناك شيء ما
I can't say in front of you.
لا أستطيع أن أقول أمامك.
I think both you and I
أعتقد أنا وأنت
will feel better doing it in this way.
ستشعر بتحسن عند القيام بذلك بهذه الطريقة.
Whether it's about mom,
سواء كان الأمر يتعلق بأمي ،
Lin Feng,
لين فنغ ،
Ding Xiang
دينغ شيانغ
♫ The falling light ♫
الضوء الساقط ♫
or Ms. Le Le,
أو السيدة  لو لو ،
♫ Leads to a road ♫
يؤدي إلى طريق ♫
I find that I really hate you.
أجد أنني أكرهك حقًا.
♫ Longing for you ♫
♫ شوق لك ♫
I never hide this.
أنا لا أخفي هذا أبدا.
♫ To be at the end ♫
أن تكون في النهاية ♫
That's why
لهذا السبب
♫ If the wind started to ♫
إذا بدأت الريح في ♫
I was so surprised
كنت متفاجأ جدا
♫ Stop chasing the rain ♫
♫ توقف عن مطاردة المطر ♫
you came to save me.
أتيت لإنقاذي.
♫ How would the eyes ♫
كيف العيون ♫
I realized
أدركت
♫ Fog up? ♫
♫ ضباب؟  ♫
you're right.
أنت على حق.
♫ Listen to ♫
♫ استمع إلى ♫
♫ All the diversity in the world ♫
♫ كل التنوع في العالم ♫
The world
العالم
is totally different from what I imagined.
يختلف تمامًا عما تخيلته.
♫ But time ♫
♫ لكن الوقت ♫
♫ Is still flying ♫
♫ ما زالت تطير ♫
There are two sides to everything.
هناك وجهان لكل شيء.
♫ How many reunions ♫
♫ كم عدد لم الشمل ♫
Bastards like you
الأوغاد مثلك
♫ Does it take ♫
هل يستغرق
♫ To understand ♫
لفهم ♫
will also be weak inside.
سيكون أيضًا ضعيفًا من الداخل.
♫ A touch? ♫
♫ لمسة؟  ♫
There are mean things
هناك أشياء لئيمة
behind all the good things I think.
وراء كل الأشياء الجيدة التي أعتقدها.
♫ The sea chants for the sky ♫
♫ البحر يهتف للسماء ♫
You said that the lions on the grassland
قلت أن الأسود على المراعي
♫ With the raging of the waves ♫
مع احتدام الأمواج ♫
will let their cubs grow wildly.
سوف تترك أشبالهم تنمو بعنف.
♫ Make a wish ♫
♫ تمنى أمنية ♫
♫ On an ordinary night ♫
في ليلة عادية ♫
In this way,
في هذا الطريق،
they can slowly stand on their own
يمكنهم الوقوف ببطء بمفردهم
♫ Praying that the red eyes ♫
الدعاء ان احمرار العيون ♫
and survive on the competitive grassland.
والبقاء على قيد الحياة في المراعي التنافسية.
♫ Are no longer blurry ♫
♫ لم تعد ضبابية
♫ Look up and watch ♫
♫ ابحث و شاهد
Now I finally realize.
الآن أدركت أخيرًا.
♫ The starry sky ♫
♫ السماء المرصعة بالنجوم ♫
♫ I hold you ♫
♫ أنا أمسكك ♫
Tear away the gorgeous appearance
تمزيق المظهر الرائع
and stay in it.
والبقاء فيه.
♫ With all my love ♫
♫ مع كل حبي ♫
I can understand the truth of life.
أستطيع أن أفهم حقيقة الحياة.
♫ Can you hear my wish ♫
♫ هل تسمع رغبتي ♫
♫ In the noise? ♫
♫ في الضجيج؟  ♫
I just found out that
لقد اكتشفت ذلك للتو
♫ Perhaps you can understand it ♫
♫ ربما تستطيع أن تفهمه ♫
I've been demanding
كنت أطالب
from you all these years,
منك كل هذه السنوات ،
♫ Only if you are ♫
فقط إذا كنت ♫
but I've never offered anything.
لكني لم أعرض أي شيء قط.
♫ Closer to me ♫
أقرب إلي ♫
I even
أنا حتى
treated you coldly.
عاملتك ببرود.
I only contradict you.
أنا فقط أعارضك.
I just want to make you angrier
أنا فقط أريد أن أجعلك أكثر غضبا
and more disappointed in me.
وأكثر خيبة أمل في.
I've never loved you
لم أحبك أبدًا
or cared about you.
أو يهتم بك.
I feel very guilty
أشعر بالذنب الشديد
about my unkind words to you.
عن كلماتي غير اللطيفة لك.
♫ Who's waiting ♫
♫ من ينتظر ♫
But after so many things,
لكن بعد أشياء كثيرة ،
♫ To be touched softly ♫
♫ أن يلمسها بهدوء
I gradually realize
أدركت تدريجيا
♫ Promises shouldn't be like ♫
لا ينبغي أن تكون الوعود مثل ♫
how important family is.
ما مدى أهمية الأسرة.
Silly girl.
فتاة سخيفة.
♫ A gust of wind ♫
♫ زوبعة ريح ♫
♫ How many times ♫
♫ كم مرة ♫
I didn't cherish you
أنا لم أعزك
♫ Shall I whisper ♫
هل سأهمس ♫
♫ To be enough to describe ♫
أن يكون كافيا لوصف ♫
when you were with me.
عندما كنت معي.
♫ Love? ♫
♫ حب؟  ♫
I didn't know
لم أكن أعرف
how important you were
كم كنتم مهمين
♫ The sea chants for the sky ♫
♫ البحر يهتف للسماء ♫
until you were not here.
حتى لم تكن هنا.
♫ With the raging of the waves ♫
مع احتدام الأمواج ♫
Dad.
أب.
♫ Make a wish ♫
♫ تمنى أمنية ♫
Silly girl.
فتاة سخيفة.
You're not a good person,
أنت لست شخصًا جيدًا ،
♫ On an ordinary night ♫
في ليلة عادية ♫
but you're a good father.
لكنك أب جيد.
♫ Praying that the red eyes ♫
الدعاء ان احمرار العيون ♫
♫ Are no longer blurry ♫
♫ لم تعد ضبابية
And I found that
ووجدت ذلك
♫ Look up and watch ♫
♫ ابحث و شاهد
I not only hate you
أنا لا أكرهك فقط
♫ The starry sky ♫
♫ السماء المرصعة بالنجوم ♫
but also love you.
بل احبك ايضا.
♫ I hold you ♫
♫ أنا أمسكك ♫
♫ With all my love ♫
♫ مع كل حبي ♫
♫ Can you hear my wish ♫
♫ هل تسمع رغبتي ♫
♫ In the noise? ♫
♫ في الضجيج؟  ♫
Do you know that?
هل تعرف أن؟
♫ Perhaps you can understand it ♫
♫ ربما تستطيع أن تفهمه ♫
I love you so much.
أنا أحبك جداً.
♫ Only if you are ♫
فقط إذا كنت ♫
I love you,
أحبك،
♫ Closer to me ♫
أقرب إلي ♫
Yun Er.
يون ار.
I love you.
أحبك.
[After the hearing, they received a fair trial]
[بعد الجلسة ، حصلوا على محاكمة عادلة]
[Zhang Hao Cheng, Li, Hunting Dog and others are suspected of]
[يشتبه في أن تشانغ هاو تشنغ ولي و Hunting Dog وآخرين]
[by the law and got the deserved punishment.]
[بالقانون ونال العقوبة المستحقة.]
[intentional homicide, illegal imprisonment,]
[القتل العمد ، السجن غير القانوني ،]
[detainment and other crimes.]
[الاعتقال وجرائم أخرى.]
There's a code vulnerability in the Pangu system of Celeste Group.
هناك ثغرة في التعليمات البرمجية في نظام Pangu التابع لمجموعة Celeste.
Many users are in a coma.
كثير من المستخدمين في غيبوبة.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
You just mentioned
لقد ذكرت للتو
the Pangu 2021 code error.
خطأ رمز Pangu 2021.
Will it get out of control
هل ستخرج عن نطاق السيطرة
as the situation gets worse?
مع تفاقم الوضع؟
I can only say that
لا يسعني إلا أن أقول ذلك
we'll fix this code error
سنقوم بإصلاح خطأ الكود هذا
at all costs as soon as possible.
بأي ثمن في أسرع وقت ممكن.
Do you feel annoyed when I talk to you like this every day?
هل تشعر بالضيق عندما أتحدث معك بهذه الطريقة كل يوم؟
You can't really hear a word?
لا يمكنك حقا سماع كلمة؟
Wei Wei said
قال وي وي
you're having a long dream.
لديك حلم طويل.
Just like Ye Tian.
تمامًا مثل يي تيان.
But you'll wake up.
لكنك ستستيقظ.
When are you going to wake up?
متى سوف تستيقظ؟
You've been dreaming for too long.
لقد كنت تحلم لفترة طويلة.
Nurse!
ممرضة!
He just moved.
لقد انتقل للتو.
He just talked.
لقد تحدث للتو.
He moved his hand.
حرك يده.
How is he?
كيف حاله؟
Xiao Qiao.
شياو تشياو.
I'm not dreaming, right?
أنا لا أحلم ، أليس كذلك؟
You're not dreaming.
أنت لا تحلم.
Your girlfriend has been taking care of you for half a month.
صديقتك كانت تعتني بك لمدة نصف شهر.
She talks to you every day.
تتحدث معك كل يوم.
Girlfriend?
صديقة؟
I'm dreaming.
أنا أحلم.
You're not.
أنت لست.
You fool.
يالك من أحمق.
Everything is normal.
كل شيئ طبيعي.
Let's call the director.
دعنا ندعو المخرج.
How do you feel?
ما هو شعورك؟
[Users who are still online]
[المستخدمون الذين لا يزالون متصلين]
[in Pangu to go offline immediately.]
[في بانغو للذهاب إلى وضع عدم الاتصال على الفور.]
[Don't do anything related to Pangu]
[لا تفعل أي شيء متعلق بـ Pangu]
[until we find a solution.]
[حتى نجد حلاً.]
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Why do you get up?
لماذا تستيقظ؟
Do you want to be in a coma again?
هل تريد الدخول في غيبوبة مرة أخرى؟
I must inform the group's senior executives
يجب أن أبلغ كبار المديرين التنفيذيين للمجموعة
that the 2021 code error
أن خطأ رمز 2021
is real.
انه حقيقي.
[Which department head]
[أي رئيس قسم]
[of Celeste Group]
[من مجموعة سيليست]
[should bear the greatest responsibility?]
[يجب أن تتحمل أكبر قدر من المسؤولية؟]
[I'll take full responsibility.]
[سأتحمل المسؤولية كاملة.]
I must go to Celeste Group now.
يجب أن أذهب إلى مجموعة سيليست الآن.
Xiao Qiao.
شياو تشياو.
Believe me.
صدقني.
They need me now.
هم بحاجة لي الآن.
[Users who are still online go offline immediately.]
[المستخدمون الذين ما زالوا متصلين بالإنترنت يصبحون بلا اتصال على الفور.]
[Don't do anything related to Pangu]
[لا تفعل أي شيء متعلق بـ Pangu]
[until we find a solution.]
[حتى نجد حلاً.]
I saw the news.
رأيت الأخبار.
It's the best decision for you
إنه أفضل قرار لك
to make 2021 public
لجعل عام 2021 عامًا
and get all users offline.
واحصل على جميع المستخدمين في وضع عدم الاتصال.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
So are you Bai Wei
إذن هل أنت باي وي
or Ye Tian now?
أو يي تيان الآن؟
It's me.
هذا أنا.
Ye Tian.
أيها تيان.
Actually,
في الواقع،
I should've expected that.
كان يجب أن أتوقع ذلك.
You won't
لن تفعل
wait inside passively
انتظر في الداخل بشكل سلبي
for me to come to you.
لي أن آتي إليك.
You actively join the core group
أنت تنضم بنشاط إلى المجموعة الأساسية
to get the authority
للحصول على السلطة
to restart the account
لإعادة الحساب
so that you can come out, right?
حتى تتمكن من الخروج ، أليس كذلك؟
So Bai Wei
لذلك باي وي
also knows what I've done.
يعرف أيضًا ما فعلته.
I like Bai Wei.
أنا أحب باي وي.
But she chose you.
لكنها اختارك.
I give in.
أنا أستسلم.
I'll also pay
سأدفع أيضًا
for my mistakes.
لأخطائي.
You're not the only one to blame.
أنت لست الوحيد الملام.
I'm also responsible
أنا أيضًا مسؤول
for the 2021 case.
لحالة 2021.
Since you're back,
منذ عودتك ،
I'll return the duty of the president
سأعيد واجب الرئيس
to you.
لك.
And me.
و أنا.
You know it as well?
هل تعرف ذلك أيضًا؟
Thank you for
شكرا لك على
taking care of Bai Wei these days.
رعاية باي وي هذه الأيام.
Don't mention it, Director Ye.
لا تذكر ذلك ، أيها المخرج.
There's something new in Pangu.
هناك شيء جديد في Pangu.
Let's go and check it out.
دعنا نذهب ونتحقق من ذلك.
Let's work together.
لنعمل معا.
I'll stay in Celeste Group
سأبقى في مجموعة سيليست
to open a channel for you to communicate.
لفتح قناة للتواصل معك.
The more you stop me,
كلما أوقفتني ،
the more interested I am in your world.
كلما كنت مهتمًا بعالمك.
When I go out,
عندما أخرج،
I'll conquer your world
سأحتل عالمك
just as I conquer Pangu.
تماما كما قهر بانغو.
Even if General Long Wei
حتى لو الجنرال لونغ وي
is made according to your cognitive chain,
مصنوع وفقًا لسلسلتك المعرفية ،
the consequences will be unimaginable
ستكون العواقب لا يمكن تصورها
if you cover him.
إذا قمت بتغطيته.
You'll even disappear completely in Pangu.
حتى أنك ستختفي تمامًا في Pangu.
I can't cover him.
لا أستطيع تغطيته.
Xiao Tian.
شياو تيان.
Kill me!
اقتلني!
Lin Feng!
لين فنغ!
Xiao Tian!
شياو تيان!
Hurry up!
عجلوا!